[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the estimated average lifespan of a crocodile?", "correct_answer": "70+ years", "incorrect_answers": ["80+ years", "50+ years", "90+ years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On July 23, 1984, Vanessa Williams became the first Miss America to give up her crown. What was the reason for this?", "correct_answer": "She had nude photos in a magazine.", "incorrect_answers": ["She was accused of bribing the jury.", "She was pregnant during the competition.", "She was accused of having breast implants."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What special gift does the young Dalai Lama receive from Tibetan monks in the beginning of the 1997 movie Seven Years in Tibet?", "correct_answer": "A music box", "incorrect_answers": ["A diamond", "A statue of Buddha", "A cat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the color of the eggs of all parrot species?", "correct_answer": "White", "incorrect_answers": ["Green", "Multicolored", "Blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Dirty Dancing, Lonny Price played the role of Robbie Gould, the waiter who gets Penny pregnant and dates Babys sister Lisa.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the title of a 1973 song by The Rolling Stones?", "correct_answer": "Silver Train", "incorrect_answers": ["Silver Boat", "Silver Car", "Silver Ride"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The idea for the 2004 movie Crash came to the director when his car was carjacked.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of an Easter egg made for the Russian Tsars between 1885 and 1917.", "correct_answer": "Faberg\u00e9 Egg", "incorrect_answers": ["Peter Egg", "Russian Egg", "Bunny Egg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Brad, a character from Fast Times at Ridgemont High, portrayed by Judge Reinhold, was fired from All American Burger, and got a job where?", "correct_answer": "Captain Hooks", "incorrect_answers": ["Long John Silvers", "A Slice Of Heaven Pizza", "Burgeritaville"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following movies contained more than one set of siblings?", "correct_answer": "The Long Riders", "incorrect_answers": ["Independence Day", "Paper Moon", "Duck Soup"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The worlds first mobile popcorn machine was introduced in Chicago, Illinois in 1885 by this man.", "correct_answer": "Charles Cretors", "incorrect_answers": ["Cloid Smith", "Felix de Azara", "Percy Spencer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All but one of the following activities are generally untypical for jaguars. Choose the one most natural to them.", "correct_answer": "Stalking and ambushing their prey", "incorrect_answers": ["Starting to eat their prey from the fleshy abdominal area", "Chasing their prey", "Attacking humans"]}]